Armando Torrez

I am a graduate of FIU with extensive experience in customer relations and account management. I am proficient in Mac, Windows, and Linux environments and can resolve operating system issues in a timely and accurate manner. I have acquired excellent communication skills through my experiences in the hospital and customer service sectors and can easily translate technical information into plain language.

 \times

atorr233@gmail.com

(305) 773-7986

in

linkedin.com/in/atorrez007

SKILLS

CompTIA A+ Certified

Mac Support

Software Troubleshooting

Cloud Computing

Customer Service

System Backup and Recovery

Networking

Help Desk

Mobile Device Support

EPIC Software

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH







ORGANIZATIONS

PHI KAPPA PHI- Honor Society

WORK EXPERIENCE

Patient Access Representative

Legacy Good Samaritan Hospital 12/2018 - Present

My responsibilities include patient preadmission, admission, transfer, and discharge activities. Work under the guidance of the Patient Access Supervisor. Contact insurance companies for medical billing operations. Interact with hospital administrations to perform effective patient operations. Work in compliance with hospital policies and procedures and adhere to government regulations.

Portland, OR

Guest Services Agent

Hotel Modera

09/2018 - 12/2018 Portland, OR

As a GSA, my job consists of registering guests in and out of their rooms, while accommodating any special requests. While checking our guests, I will verify their method of payment and run an authorization hold on the given card. Also, an important part of the job requires up-selling guest rooms, by sharing available alternatives and options.

Patient Access Representative

Memorial Regional Hospital South

02/2017 - 07/2018 Hollywood, FL

As a Patient Access Representative, my role in the company is to initiate authorizations and verify coordination of benefits for patients in the Emergency Department as well as Outpatient Services. I also communicate with the patient, on a one to one basis, about their current or outstanding accounts and coordinate a resolution primarily through payment plans.

Asset Protection Associate

Best Buy

12/2016 - 02/2017 Pembroke Pines, FL

As an Asset Protection Associate, I monitored store activity for any theft. I protected against fraudulent activity by creating protection alerts while reporting and documenting incidents properly when necessary. In addition, I coached store employees about the principles, standards, and policies related to safety and crisis events.

Customer Care and Sales Representative

Crown Linen, LLC

12/2015 - 06/2016 Miami. FL

As a Customer Care & Sales Representative at Crown Linen, I was responsible for managing the accounts of hotels involved in partnerships with the company as well as maintaining personal relationships with the corresponding hotel staff and administrative partners. I upheld customer service satisfaction at optimal levels and catered to hotels' linen operations 24 hours a day.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Criminal Justice

Florida International University

08/2014 - 05/2016 Miami, FL